

SAFIULLAH KARIMI

Web Developer

About Me

I am Safiullah Karimi, a web developer. In addition to web development, I also have computer skills, I know several programming languages, and I have many years of experience in web development, and I do my best to perform my work honestly.



+93797050890



safiullahkarimi751@gmail.com



Herat Afghanistan 18 street

LANGUAGE

- English
- Persian
- Pashto

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Laravel
- Mysql
- Java
- Account Management
- Data Entry

EXPERIENCE

Herat Host company 2021 - 2022

For one year, I worked as a web developer

lajward company 2022 - 2023

As a web developer, I have performed team work

Freelancer 2023 - 2024

Currently, after several years of working in local companies in my city, I am working online and developing Teemcha website, which is similar to Amazon's website.

EDUCATION

School graduate

Graduated from Englab Islamic High School in 2020

Herat UNIVERSITY

Graduated from Herat University with a bachelor's degree in computer science in 2024

Wassa Institute

Completion of a one and a half year training course in web development